Seitz, Peter Arbitration Files 5733
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- WFMJ Broadcasting Co. and WFMJ-TV vs. NABET, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - leaving plant without permission. (Award only).
- WFSB-TV, Pst-Newsweek Stations, Connecticut, Inc. vs. NABET, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  Issue: Successor Company - past practice. (Award only).
- WFSB-TV, Post-Newsweek Stations, Connecticut, Inc. vs. NABET, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  Issue: Scheduling - seniority. (Award only).
- WHEC, Inc. vs. NABET, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  Issue: Vacation pay. (Award only).
- WHEC, Inc. vs. NABET, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper personal conduct - detrimental conduct. (Award only).
- WPIX, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  Issue: Lunch periods - time for taking. (Award only).
- WPIX, Inc. vs. International Photographers of the Motion Picture Industries, Local 644, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - classification - special types of work. (Award only).
- WPIX, Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft of company property; termination of employment - layoff. (Award only).
- WPIX, Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  Cancelled. RC, SD.
- WPIX, Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Issue: Rates of pay. B, AN, EX, RC. (No award).
- WTFM, Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Issue: Information not available. B, RC. (No award).
- WTIC, Broadcast Plaza, Inc. vs. NABET, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Issue: Seniority - temporary employees; assignment of jobs bargaining unit work; lunch periods contract interpretation. (Award only).
- Wallingford Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 2242, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  Issue: Incentive pay and incentive systems - standards of production. (Award only).
- Wappingers Central School District vs. Wappingers Congress of Teachers, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Issue: Union security -dues deductions. (Award only).
- Washington Post Co. vs. Washington Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union Number 449; vs. Washington, D.C. Stereotypers Union 19, 1962-1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Issue: Contract modification - wage adjustments; assignment of jobs - jurisdiction. (Award only).
- Washington Publishers' Association vs. UPEU of NA, Washington Photo-Engravers Union 17; vs. Columbia Typographical Union 101, 1962-1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Issue: Contracts side agreement; Arbitrability - survival of contract rights; rates of pay - discontinuance of job. (Award only).
- Ward Baking Co. vs. IAM, District 47, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  Issue: Layoff - seniority.
- Waterbury Mattress Co. vs. UAW, Local 1141, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  Issue: Arbitrability - multiple issues; arbitrability -timeliness; schedules of work - management rights. (Award only).
- Weber, David Co. vs. UPIU, Local 375, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; absences unauthorized; rates of pay new employee. (Award only).
- Weiner, Lawrence and Associates, Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  Issue: Rates of pay. B, RC, AN, SD, EX.
- Weiner, Lawrence and Associates, Inc. vs. AFTRA, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- West Co. vs. URW, Local 827, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - overtime; absences - reporting. (Award only).
- Westinghouse Broadcasting Co., Inc. vs. IBEW Local 1228; vs. Westinghouse Television Broadcasting Studio Employees Local 833; Westinghouse vs. IATSE Local 804, 1963-1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - failure to assign, assignment of work outside unit; rates of pay - overtime. (Award Only.)
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. vs IUE, Local 130, Local 746; vs. Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Union; vs. IBEW Local 1914, 1957-1980 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; fights and altercations - assault on fellow employee; transfers - refusal by employer; dishonesty - time clock procedure; discipline - suspension; arbitrability - unfair labor practice; overtime - refusal of; discipline - vi
- White, S. S., Dental Manufacturing Co. vs. IBT, Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 169, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; plant rules - unwritten rules. (Award only).
- White Motor Corp., and its subsidiary, White Farm Equipment Co. vs. UAW, Local 932, 1147, 107 and 337, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  Issue: Fringe benefits - pension plans; management rights - unilateral action. SD, LD.
- Wilkes-Barre Publishing Co. vs. American Newspaper Guild, Local 120, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  Issue: Vacancies - management's right to determine existence of. (Award only).
- Wright Aeronautical Division vs. UAW, Local 300, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; improper personal conduct - insubordination. (Award only).
- Yale and Towne Manufacturing Co. vs. IAM, Local 117, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  Issue: Recall - following strike. (Award Only.)
- Yale University vs. Federation of University Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 35, 1973-1977 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  Issue: Termination of employment - discharge vs quits; absences - notice - in general; management rights - reorganization of job classifications; schedules of work - shift scheduling. (Award Only.)
- General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  January-February; Between Seitz and Ben Falcigno, Assistant Director of Conciliation, New York State Public Employee Relations Board (NYSPERB), re working guidelines for arbitration agreed to by New York State and Council 82, AFSCME. Seitz refuses to serv
- General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  March-May; With Charles O. Gregory re personal and arbitration cases; with Lee Lowen Fish re Messersmith case; with Chalmer M. Roberts, personal; and other routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  June; 3 page letter to the editor, Chronicle of Higher Education, re the Yoshiva University case and unionization of private institutions; substantial correspondence between Frederick U. Reel, arbitrator and Peter Seitz re "obey and grieve" rule; and rout
- General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  July-Sept. Correspondence between Frederick U. Reel and Seitz, continued; and routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  October; 3 page letter to editors, Columbia Journalism Review, from Marvin J. Miller, Acting President Major League Baseball Players Association (WCC to Seitz) re article about the baseball strike and sports reporting; personal and routine.
- General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  Nov-Dec; Additional correspondence with Charles O. Gregory; letter to Inspector General, U.S. Postal Service re commendation of a particular witness, Inspector Kyanko, during post office strike; and routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  January-March; With C. O. Gregory; between Seitz and Columbia Journalism Review re baseball dispute (1980) article by Mr. Crane; with Alfred Friendly re personal; routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  April-May; With Joseph Sirefman, attorney, re musicians/labor relations; "hate mail" from a grievant; personal along with poetry by Seitz to Harold L. Enarson, President, Ohio State University; to C. E. Harwood, Torrington Co. re Seitz' views on suspensio
- General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  June; Personal with C. O. Gregory; to Marvin Miller, Major League Baseball Players Association re baseball dispute; correspondence re paper delivered by Seitz at the American Symphony Orchestra League and personal and routine.
- General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  July-Aug; To Archibald Cox, Chairman, Common Cause, re an article by Cox; additional with Red Smith; additional with C. O. Gregory; with Associated Press re Seitz being misquoted during baseball strike.
- General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  Sept.-Oct.; With Sidney Wolff, arbitrator, re an article by Seitz; and routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  Nov.-Dec; To editor, Wall Street Journal, re interest arbitration; additional personal with Alfred Friendly; letter to another individual with the name "Peter Seitz" charging him as an "imposter"; personal and routine.
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  Jan-Feb; With Willard Wirtz re personal; with Martin E. Segal re personal; other routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  March; With Bill Bradley, U.S. Senate re personal; to Joseph Barbash re a biographical sketch from Seitz for an upcoming conference; other personal and routine.
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  April-May; Routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  June-July; With Arrid Anderson re personal; with Judge Harry Edwards, U.S. Court of Appeals re socializing with parties involved in arbitration disputes; to Benjamin Aaron, University of California re personal; to Patrick Moynihan, U.S. Senator re ERA; ro
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  Aug to Sept; Routine and personal.
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  Oct.-Nov.; Poetry sent to New York Times and Marvin Miller Major League Baseball Players Association; substantial correspondence and printouts with Labor Relations Press re biographical material for directory of arbitrators; with Bowie Kuhn, Commissioner,
- General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  December; With A. H. Raskin re personal; additional with Eva Robbins re personal and routine; to editor, Sports Sections, New York Times re "free agents"; routine and personal.
- Documentation re Davis-Bacon Act, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  correspondence, reports recommendations.
- Documentation re Davis-Bacon Act, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Miscellaneous unpublished NBA arbitration decisions issued by Impartial Chairmen prior to Peter Seitz, 1968-1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Eckert decisions - Blefary, 1st Class Hotel, Cole Decisions - Players Pool, Pedro Ramos
- NBA and NBPA, 1972-1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Agreements and rule-reference book
- Major League Baseball Players Association - Agreements and Baseball Blue Book, 1968-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Rules and Regulations
- Miscellaneous NBA Documents, 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Court cases, agreements, correspondence
- Article - Sports Enter the Labor Arena, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Fall Issue of Industrial and Labor Relations Report
- Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  Newspaper clippings, correspondence, essays, press releases, speeches
- Article - A Crack in the Dike: The Story of Baseball Salary Arbitration 1973-75, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Ken Haas, Harvard Law School, April, also includes correspondence
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Awards, 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  American Arbitration Association, American Newspaper Guild Arbitration Reports
- Photograph of Seitz (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Trans World Airlines vs. IAM, System Board of Adjustment, 1978 (Box 23, Folder All)
  TR, EX, AN, SD.
- Trans World Airlines vs. IAM, System Board of Adjustment, 1978 (Box 24, Folder All)